120 is a history, drama, war film directed by Özhan Eren.
During the Sarikamis Battle, the Ottoman army runs out of ammunition and
appeals to the people of Van for help, who happen to have supplies.
However, the First World War is on and all men are fighting at four corners
of the empire and therefore can not respond to to the appeal.
The young children of Van want to do something...
Münire, played by Özge Özberk.
Sermet Bey, played by Burak Sergen.
Süleyman, played by Cansel Elçin.
Cemal Müdür, played by Emin Olcay.
Kamil Pasa, played by Demir Karahan.
120 is a 2008 Turkish war film directed by Murat Saraçoğlu and Özhan Eren based on the true story of 120 children who
died in 1915 carrying ammunition for the Battle of Sarikamish against the Russians during World War I.
The film went on general release across Turkey on February 15, 2008
(2008-02-15) and is one of the highest grossing Turkish films of 2008.
The film explores themes of mountain, munition, turkey.
The tone is emotional.